RAFAL KRUSZEWSKI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

085 78 09 516

dev.rafalq@gmail.com

https://rafalq.github.io/latest-cv/

Galway City, Ireland

SKILLS

FRONTEND

HTML | CSS

Javascript | Typescript | Vue js | React

BACKEND

Node js | Express js

Python | Django | Flask

PHP | Laravel

MySql | mongoDB

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer

Code Institute, Ireland

2019-2020

Java Associate Developer SE 8

ecollege, Ireland

2018-2019

Philosophy

Poznan University, Poland

2002-2005

Political Science

Pawel Wlodkowic College, Poland

1999-2001

LANGUAGES

Polish: native

English: advanced

PROFILE

I'm a Full Stack Developer with diverse interests and great enthusiasm that I bring to every project. I follow form as well as function.

I know that the aesthetics of effective design combined with application speed, security and reliability combine to create a great user experience.

I work effectively in getting things. I'm a keen team player who thrives in bright and enthusiastic teams and I'm also a self starter when working solo.

CERTIFICATES

Diploma of Software Developement | Code Institute

Certificate of Java Foundations | Oracle

Certificate of completion for Modern React and Redux | Udemy

Certificate of completion for Ultimate Mysql Bootcamp | Udemy

Certificate of completion for Go For Beginners Crash Course | Udemy

Certificate of completion for Golang The Practical Guide | Academind

Certificate of paritcipating in Vue.js Forge | vueschool

WORK EXPERIENCE

General Operative

Medtronic CardioVascular, Galway, Ireland

2007-2017

Working on a production line. Product Assembly and inspection through the use of a microscope. Handling fragile products. Using equipment and machinery. Performing quality checks – ensuring he product meets the required standard. Packaging and labeling of products. Communication with supervisors and peers. Accurately completing documentation.

Radio Journalist Assistant

Radio Boss, Poland

1995-1999

Generating and developing original ideas for the programme. Researching items, edit, and script briefs. Booking and maintaining relationships with show guests. Developing new angles and contributors on existing stories. Creatively communicating show content across all platforms to drive listenership figures. Editing relevant sound clips.

REFERENCES

Available upon request.